// History
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Who is the founder of Haryanka Dynasty?",
    answer: "Bimbisara",
    options: [
      "Ajatashatru",
      "Harshvardhan",
      "Bimbisara",
      "Ghananand"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The Moplah Rebellion in 1921 in Malabar was Muslim Peasants Rabellion against ",
    answer: "Hindu Land Holders",
    options: [
      "Muslim Land Holders",
      "The British Government Authority",
      "The non-tribal outsiders",
      "Hindu Land Holders"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The Rowlatt Act was passed in:",
    answer: "1919",
    options: [
      "1919",
      "1905",
      "1913",
      "1925"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Mahatma Gandhi launched Kheda Satyagrah on Gujrat in 1918 to support the cause of ",
    answer: "The peasants",
    options: [
      "Land Lords",
      "The peasants",
      "Mill Owners",
      "Kol Rebellion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Two of the great Mughals wrote their own memories. They were",
    answer: "Babar and Jahangir",
    options: [
      "Babar and Humayun",
      "Humayun and Jahangir",
      "Jahangir and Shahjahan",
      "Babar and Jahangir"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Lala Lajpat Rai was also known as :",
    answer: "Sher-e-Punjab",
    options: [
      "Sher-e-Bengal",
      "Sher-e-Punjab",
      "Sher-e-Maharastra",
      "Sher-e-Kashmir"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "To which king belongs the Lion capital at Sarnath?",
    answer: "Ashoka",
    options: [
      "Ashoka",
      "Kanishka",
      "Chandragupta",
      "Harshavardhan"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The language of discourses of Gautama Buddha was",
    answer: "Pali",
    options: [
      "Bhojpuri",
      "Magadhi",
      "Sanskrit",
      "Pali"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The Hindu Dharma Sangrakshini Sabha was formed in :",
    answer: "1893",
    options: [
      "1872",
      "1883",
      "1886",
      "1893"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Bande Matram was a series of articles published in the year 1907 by :",
    answer: "Sri Aurobindo Ghosh",
    options: [
      "Bal Gangadhar Tilak",
      "Sri Aurobindo Ghosh",
      "Domadar Chapekar",
      "Balkrishana Chapekar"
    ]
  },
];